smarthealthshop.com 2019-05-09

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy:**

 **DH Smart Health Shop** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.

 **General Statement of Principles**  
As described in detail below, any information we gather at this web site is strictly for our use and is not shared with any other entity, public or private, for any reason - period. We will not sell or give away any lists or other data that we may retain and we do not purchase such information from other sources.

 **Statistical Data**  
Our servers (as most) track IP addresses and referring pages to help with site maintenance and improvements. This data is viewed only as anonymous statistics to show the busiest times of the day or week, pages with errors and how effective our advertising has been. This information is not used for any other purpose.

 **Personal Information Collected - Order Forms**  
With the exception of credit card information, we store the information from your order form to allow us to track consulting issues or refer to a previous order to help provide some customer service. You may elect to have your information completely removed from this system by e-mailing us at [support@smarthealthshop.com](mailto:support@smarthealthshop.com) with your request. We do not store any type of credit card information.

 **Information Correction or Removal**  
If you wish to correct, update or remove any information about you that may be in our records, please send us e-mail at [support@smarthealthshop.com](mailto:support@smarthealthshop.com) with the details of your request. If you wish to contact us further, please find complete contact information on our [contact](http://www.smarthealthshop.com/?route=information/contact) page.

 _Updated May, 2018_

On 25 May 2018, the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) replaces the existing 1995 EU Data Protection Directive (European Directive 95/46/EC). DH Smart Health Shop is committed to GDPR compliance, and we have evaluated the new requirements and restrictions imposed by the GDPR as well as have reviewed where and how we collect, use, store and dispose of personal data and updating policies, standards and documentation as necessary.

The following Privacy Policy is a reviewed version dated by May, 2018 that complies with the Regulation.

### BY USING THE WEBSITE, YOU CONSENT TO OUR COLLECTION, USE, AND DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION AS DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

## WHAT TYPE OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT

Non-Personally Identifiable Information. SmartHealthshop.com collects non-personally identifiable information that your browser makes available whenever you visit a website. This information includes your Internet connection and hardware specs, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your query and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

Personally Identifiable Information. In addition, we collect your personal information such as your full name, credit card information, billing address, your email address, history of communication with SmartHealthShop.com, history of payments, IP address, system information, and your activities on the Website.

We do not collect your sensitive personal information, in particular, confidential medical facts, racial or ethnic origins, political or religious beliefs or sexuality.

If we hold any information about you which is incorrect or if there are any changes to your details or if you wish to see a copy of the information that we hold about you, please let us know at support@smarthealthshop.com so that we can keep our records accurate and up to date. You are also free to contact us regarding deletion of some or of all information we have gathered about you.

Additionally and only upon your grant of respective permissions we may collect information from third party service providers.

## HOW WE COLLECT THE INFORMATION

Cookie Policies. “Cookies” are small text files which are transferred from our website, product or service and stored on your computer’s hard drive. We use a combination of cookies to help us provide you with a personalised service, and also to help make our websites, products and services better for you. You are able to configure your browser to restrict or block cookies and similar technologies if you wish, however if you disable those you may find this affects your ability to use certain parts of our website, products or services.

## HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION

Personally Identifiable Information. We use the personally identifiable user information that we collect to provide any information and services that you have requested or any products that you have ordered. We may also contact you for feedback on your use of our products, services or our website.

We may use and analyse the information that we collect so that we can administer, support, improve and develop the current services offerings, to develop new services, to be able to tailor the services to one’s specific needs if feasible, for convenience of users and communication with them.

## DISCLOSURE

Disclosure to Third-Parties. SmartHealthShop.com does not share your personal information with third parties or the public except as set forth herein. We may share your personal information with our third-party service providers, such as SMTP infrastructure providers, analytical services, payment processors, merchants, or resellers, performing services, which supplement our business. These service providers may have access to personal information as needed to perform their functions. Third parties with whom we share your data currently include, but are not limited to Google, YouTube, Facebook, and Twitter. We do not sell your personal information.

Research. We may use and disclose to third parties information we collect in aggregated, non-personally identifiable form for research and informational purposes and to help us make sales, marketing and business decisions.

Mergers and Acquisitions. If SmartHealthShop.com is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, we will continue to ensure the confidentiality of any personal information and give affected users notice before personal information is transferred or becomes subject to any new privacy policy of an acquirer of our business.

Special Circumstances. SmartHealthShop.com will not disclose your personally identifiable information except in subsections below:

  * when requested to do so by law enforcement agencies;
  * when obliged to do so under the law;
  * for the purpose of pursuing outstanding debts or liabilities;
  * and when given permission to do so by you.

Use of Information for Commercial Purposes. You may object to the use of your personal data for commercial purpose at any time by contacting us at support@smarthealthshop.com.

## INFORMATION STORAGE

Permission to Use Information. By submitting your personal information, you agree to its transfer, storage or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

We will store your usage data until such time when you withdraw your consent for us to do so. All other data as specified above will be retained for as long as is necessary for the purpose(s) for which we originally collected it. We may also retain information as required by law.

Password. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain services or specific areas of the Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask that you do not share your password with anyone.

Disclaimer. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to us via the Internet; any such transmission is at your own risk.

## INFORMATION SECURITY

Security Measures. We protect your personal information using technical and administrative security measures to reduce the risks of loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure and alteration. Some of the safeguards we use are firewalls and data encryption, physical access controls to our data centers, and information access authorization controls. For more information about staying safe while buying and selling online, or to report an issue with your account please contact us at: support@smarthealthshop.com.

Be Aware. To prevent being a phishing website victim, always check domain details when you are providing your personal information. Please, be aware that if you suspect the website you are on is a fake site representing to be SmartHealthShop.com or to provide the services, contact us directly at support@smarthealthshop.com.

Controlling Your Personal Information. SmartHealthShop.com may, from time to time, make available to users chat rooms, forums, message boards, and other interactive features. You should be aware that when you voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information (e.g. user name, e-mail address) via blog, forums, postings, profiles or other areas of the Website, that information, along with any substantive information disclosed in your communication, can be collected, correlated and used by third parties and may result in unsolicited messages from other posters or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of SmartHealthShop.com. Please do not post any personal information on the Website or in other areas that you expect to keep private.

Links. For your convenience, we may provide links to certain third party websites or referrals to certain third parties’ products or services. If you choose to visit a third party’s website or use its products or services, please be aware that the third party’s privacy policy, and not this Privacy Policy, will govern your activities and any information you disclose while interacting with the third party.

Social media platforms and widgets. Our Websites include social media features, such as the Facebook Like button. These features may collect information about your IP address and which page you are visiting on our Website, and they may set a cookie to make sure the feature functions properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Website. We also maintain presences on social media platforms including Facebook, Twitter, and YouTube. Any information, communications, or materials you submit to us via a social media platform is done at your own risk without any expectation of privacy. We cannot control the actions of other users of these platforms or the actions of the platforms themselves. Your interactions with those features and platforms are governed by the privacy policies of the companies that provide them.

## USERS’ RIGHTS

  * User has the right to amend and correct the provided data in a personal account;
  * User can change or delete his/her personal data in the user account;
  * User has the right to review his/her personal data and demand to transfer or delete this data;
  * User has the right to restrict collection and processing of data;
  * User is entitled to get his/her personal data anonymized.

## COMPLIANCE AND COOPERATION WITH REGULATORY AUTHORITIES

We regularly review our compliance with our Privacy Policy. We also adhere to several self-regulatory frameworks. When we receive formal written complaints, we will contact the person who made the complaint to follow up. We work with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that we cannot resolve with our users directly.

## COLLECTION OF INFORMATION FROM CHILDREN

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information relating to children. In the event that we learn that we have collected personally identifiable information from anyone under 18 years of age without prior parental consent, we will take steps to promptly delete such information. By providing your personal information to SmartHealthShop.com, through the Service, you represent that you are at least 18 years of age or older.

## TRANSFERS OUTSIDE EUROPE

Personal data in the European Union is protected by data protection laws but other countries do not necessarily protect your personal data in the same way. Our website and some of our products or services or parts of them may be hosted in the United States and this means that we may transfer any information which is submitted by you through the website, product or service outside the European Economic Area (which means all the EU countries plus Norway, Iceland and Liechtenstein) (“EEA”) to the United States. When you send an email to us, this may also be stored on email servers which are hosted in the United States or outside the EU. We have taken steps to ensure that our hosting provider uses the necessary level of protection for your information but if you do not want your information to be transferred outside the EEA you should not use our website, product or service or contact us via email.

## NO ERROR-FREE PERFORMANCE

SmartHealthShop.com does not guarantee error-free performance under this Privacy Policy. We may not always catch an unintended privacy issue, despite our reasonable efforts to do so. Accordingly, we welcome your feedback regarding any privacy concerns that you may have, including how we can improve this Privacy Policy. We will use reasonable efforts to comply with this Privacy Policy and will take prompt corrective action when we learn of any failure to comply with it.

## CONTACT INFORMATION

Your privacy matters to SmartHealthShop.com so whether you are new to SmartHealthShop.com or a long time user, please do take the time to get to know our practices. Questions, comments and requests regarding this Privacy Policy are welcomed and should be addressed to us by email at support@smarthealthshop.com

### Bestsellers

#### [Energy Pills: Jumpstart Ex](http://www.smarthealthshop.com/energy-pills-jumpstart-extreme)

Quantity: 30 Capsules Serving Size: 3 Capsules Jumpstart Ex is an incredible stimulant that ..

$19.77 $21.97

#### [Virility EX Pills](http://www.smarthealthshop.com/virility-ex-pills)

Virility Ex is the All-Natural Male Enhancement Pill that Works Synergistically with Exercise to Int..

$39.77 $59.97

#### [8 Hour Energy Pills](http://www.smarthealthshop.com/8-hour-energy-pills)

Quantity: 100 Capsules Serving Size: 3 Capsules Finally, an Energy Pill that WORKS as Hard a..

$35.77 $39.97

#### [Appetite Away Pills](http://www.smarthealthshop.com/appetite-away-pills)

Quantity: 30 Capsules Serving Size: 3 Capsules Appetite Away: A Weight Loss Formula and Powe..

$14.77 $15.97
